# **Baker Prescott**

# Senior Frontend Developer

• AUSTIN, TX 78748

10/12/1990

#### **Profile**

Bringing more than 12 years of experience leading website design projects, including gathering user requirements, producing code, creating mockups and enhancing designs. Focused on creating clean, robust code with exceptional security. Achieves compatibility targets while meeting and exceeding customer demands.

#### Skills

#### Frontend

ReactJS, AngularJS, VueJS, React Native, NextJS, NuxtJS, React Native

## **Content Management System**

WordPress, Shopify, Strapi

### **Database Management Systems**

MySQL, MongoDB, SQL Server

#### Backend

NodeJS, ExpressJS, Laravel, PHP, Java, Python, RESTful API, Webpack

#### **Version Control Tools**

Git(Github, Gitlab), SVN

### **DevOps**

AWS, Docker, Kubernetes

# **Professional Experience**

**TRUSTLE,** Senior Full Stack Engineer

07/2020 - 03/2023

Walnut Creek, United States

Led a team of 5 developers in delivering several high-visibility projects, including large-scale applications using Next.js, AngularJS, Nuxt.js, Node/ExpressJS, Laravel, MySQL, and MongoDB from scratch resulting in a 20% increase in application productivity.

**GOTZSYS,** Senior Full Stack Engineer

07/2017 - 06/2020

Porto Alegre, Brazil

Developed and maintained e-commerce & healthcare products using React, NodeJS, MySQL, and MongoDB.

Worked in Agile methodologies for development to deliver better applications and used Jira and Git as version control and tracking units.

**DEVNOLOGY,** Software Developer

07/2014 - 06/2017

Belo Horizonte, Brazil

Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, AJAX, and JSON coding and coded websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery languages.

Provided front-end website development using WordPress, Shopify, and other editing software.

**Freelancer,** *Software Developer* 

10/2011 - 06/2014

## **Education**

**State University of Santa Cruz,** Bachelor of Science in Computer Science / Computer Science

04/2007 - 09/2011 | Ilhéus, Brazil